{
  "Questions": [
    {"QuestionText": "Sometimes dragged behind boats to catch fish.", "Answer": "Nets"},
    {"QuestionText": "Term for all carnivorous birds characterized by sharp talons, a hooked beak, and keen eyesight.", "Answer": "Raptors"},
    {"QuestionText": "Several $1 Bills, perhaps.", "Answer": "Bucks"},
    {"QuestionText": "Large mammals used for events in Pamplona, Spain.", "Answer": "Bulls"},
    {"QuestionText": "The Saturn V, Falcon 9, and SLS, for example. ", "Answer": "Rockets"},
    {"QuestionText": "This four letter word has a base worth of 29 in scrabble.", "Answer": "Jazz"},
    {"QuestionText": "As a verb it means urges or goads onward.", "Answer": "Spurs"},
    {"QuestionText": "Fast, 19th-century sailing vessels characterized by sleek, streamlined hulls, sharp bows, and large sail area, designed for speed over cargo capacity.", "Answer": "Clippers"},
    {"QuestionText": "Supporters of Charles I in the English Civil War.", "Answer": "Cavaliers"},
    {"QuestionText": "Vociferously pedals goods, often in a public place.", "Answer": "Hawks"}
  ]
}